Inventory of the William J. Casey papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- PRIVATE LIFE FILE, 1976-1981 (Boxes 195-282)
  - Subject file
    - American Bar Association
      - General (Box-folder 227: 7)
      - Committee on Education about Communism (Box-folder 227: 8)
      - Committee on Law and International Security (Box-folder 228: 1-2)
      - International Law Section (Box-folder 228: 3)
      - Subcommittee on International Securities Regulation (Box-folder 228: 4)
    - American-Chilean Council (Box-folder 228: 5)
    - American Committee on the History of the Second World War (Box-folder 228: 6)
    - American Council for Coordinated Action (Box-folder 228: 7)
    - American Express Company (Box-folder 228: 8)
    - American-Israel Chamber of Commerce and Industry (Box-folder 228: 9)
    - American Petroleum Institute (Box-folder 229: 1-2)
    - American Stock Exchange. Advisory Committee on Governance
      - Minutes and meeting materials (Box-folder 229: 3)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 229: 4)
      - Memoranda (Box-folder 230: 1)
      - Report (untitled)
        - Working materials (Box-folder 230: 2)
        - Final version, 1979 June 8 (Box-folder 230: 3)
      - Board of Governors documents (Box-folder 230: 4)
      - Background materials (Box-folder 230: 5)
      - Printed matter. Includes press coverage (Box-folder 230: 6)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 231: 1)
    - Andersen Energy, Inc. (Box-folder 231: 2)
    - Angevinière Bombard (company) (Box-folder 231: 3)
    - Antitrust policy (Box-folder 231: 4)
    - Association of Former Intelligence Officers (Box-folder 231: 5)
    - Association of the Bar of the City of New York (Box-folder 232: 1)
    - Atlantic Council of the United States
      - Board of Directors documents (Box-folder 232: 2)
      - Working Group on Development Problems
        - Correspondence, meeting materials, and working materials (Box-folder 232: 3)
        - Report. "The United States and the Developing Countries"
          - Draft, 1976 June (Box-folder 232: 4)
          - Draft, 1976 September (Box-folder 232: 5)
          - Draft, 1976 November (Box-folder 232: 6)
      - Working Group on Summit Meetings and Collective Leadership
        - Correspondence and meeting materials (Box-folder 233: 1)
        - Report. "Summits and Collective Leadership in the 1980s." Drafts and final version, 1980 March 6 (Box-folder 233: 2)
      - Working Group on the Credibility of the NATO Deterrent. Correspondence and meeting materials (Box-folder 233: 3)
    - Auditing standards for lawyers (Box-folder 233: 4)
    - Automotive engines (Box-folder 233: 5)
    - Ayco Corporation (Box-folder 233: 6)
    - Bacon House (Box-folder 233: 7)
    - Bank of Greece (Box-folder 233: 8)
    - Bar Association of Nassau County, New York (Box-folder 233: 9)
    - Barter exchange (Box-folder 233: 10)
    - Boodle's (club, London, England) (Box-folder 233: 11)
    - Bruckner Medical League (Box-folder 233: 12)
    - Business Council for International Understanding (Box-folder 233: 13)
    - Calvin Bullock Forum (Box-folder 233: 14)
    - Capital Cities Communications, Inc. (Box-folder 233: 15)
    - Capital gains tax (Box-folder 233: 16)
    - Cardinal's Committee for Education (Archdiocese of New York) (Box-folder 233: 17)
    - Catholic Charities (Diocese of Rockville Centre, New York)
      - Minutes and meeting materials (Box-folder 234: 1)
      - Correspondence and memoranda (Box-folder 234: 2)
      - Reports (Box-folder 234: 3)
    - Catholic League for Religious and Civil Rights (Box-folder 234: 4)
    - Center for Energy Policy and Research (Box-folder 234: 5)
    - Center for Strategic and International Studies (Box-folder 234: 6)
    - Center for the Study of the Presidency (Box-folder 234: 7)
    - Central Intelligence Agency (Box-folder 234: 8)
    - Chairmen's Club of Nassau County (New York) (Box-folder 234: 9)
    - China. Patrick M. Boarman, "'Normalization' and Trade with China" (Box-folder 235: 1)
    - Claims, Purchase of (Box-folder 235: 2)
    - Club El Morocco (New York City) (Box-folder 235: 3)
    - Committee for Responsible Health Care
      - Articles of incorporation and bylaws (Box-folder 235: 4)
      - Minutes and meeting materials (Box-folder 235: 5)
      - Policy statements and brochures (Box-folder 235: 6)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 235: 7)
      - Memoranda (Box-folder 235: 8)
      - Background materials (Box-folder 235: 9)
    - Committee for Small Business Innovation
      - Correspondence and printed matter (Box-folder 236: 1)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 236: 2)
    - Committee on the Present Danger (Box-folder 236: 3)
    - Committee to Preserve the Dwight D. Eisenhower National Republican Center (Box-folder 236: 4)
    - Concorde (airplane) (Box-folder 236: 5)
    - Conflict of interest (legal ethics) (Box-folder 236: 6)
    - Continental Capital Corporation (Box-folder 236: 7)
    - Corporate directors (Box-folder 236: 8)
    - Corporate directors' liabilities and responsibilities (Box-folder 237: 1)
    - Corporate governance (Box-folder 237: 2)
    - Council on Foreign Relations
      - General (Box-folder 237: 3)
      - Discussion Group on Intelligence (Box-folder 237: 4)
    - Creek (club, Locust Valley, New York) (Box-folder 237: 5)
    - D-Cube Inc. (Box-folder 237: 6)
    - Dailey and Associates (Box-folder 237: 7)
    - Databases (Box-folder 237: 8)
    - Delcrete Corporation (Box-folder 237: 9)
    - Diamond Distributors, Inc. (Box-folder 237: 10)
    - Direct sea-to-air refueling (Box-folder 237: 11)
    - Disclosure policies and guidelines (securities industry) (Box-folder 238: 1)
    - Ditchley Foundation (Box-folder 238: 2)
    - Dun and Bradstreet, Inc. (Box-folder 238: 3)
    - Economic Development Council of New York City (Box-folder 238: 4)
    - Editions (booksellers) (Box-folder 238: 5)
    - El Paso Natural Gas Company (Box-folder 238: 6)
    - Elections--1978
      - Perry Duryea New York gubernatorial campaign (Box-folder 238: 7)
      - Mike Roth New York attorney general campaign (Box-folder 238: 8)
    - Employee stock ownership and pension plans (Box-folder 238: 9-10)
    - Energy
      - Speeches by others (Box-folder 239: 1)
      - Printed matter (Box-folder 239: 2-4)
      - Printed matter (contd.) (Box-folder 240: 1)
    - Energy Transition Corporation (Box-folder 240: 2)
    - Estate planning (Box-folder 240: 3)
    - Eurocommunism. Roy Godson and Stephen Haseler, "'Eurocommunism': Implications for East and West" (Box-folder 240: 4)
    - Everglades Club (Palm Beach, Florida) (Box-folder 240: 5)
    - Executive placement agencies (Box-folder 241: 1)
    - Experimental Center for the Advancement of Invention and Innovation (Box-folder 241: 2)
    - Export-Import Bank of the United States (Box-folder 241: 3-4)
    - F. M. Carter and Associates (Box-folder 241: 5)
    - Fedders Corporation (Box-folder 241: 6)
    - Federal City Club (Washington, D.C.) (Box-folder 241: 7)
    - Fiduciary Counsel, Inc. (Box-folder 241: 8)
    - Film Five Associates (Box-folder 241: 9)
    - Fine Arts Museum of Long Island (Box-folder 241: 10)
    - First Investment Annuity Company of America (Box-folder 241: 11)
    - Fitch Investors Service (Box-folder 242: 1-2)
    - Fordham University (Box-folder 242: 3)
    - Foreign affairs (Box-folder 242: 4)
    - Foreign economic policy
      - General (Box-folder 242: 5)
      - Boretsky, Michael, "Toward a New Economic Game Plan" (Box-folder 242: 6)
      - Congressional reports (Box-folder 243: 1)
    - Foreign payments and boycott regulations (Box-folder 243: 2)
    - France-America Society (Box-folder 243: 3)
    - Fraser Institute (Box-folder 243: 4)
    - Friends of the Nassau County [New York] Museum (Box-folder 244: 1)
    - Gamble-Skogmo, Inc. (Box-folder 244)
    - Correspondence, minutes, meeting materials, and printed matter (Box-folder 244: 2)
    - Reports and financial statements (Box-folder 244: 3-4)
    - Garden City Hotel (Garden City, New York) (Box-folder 244: 5)
    - General Contractors Association of New York (Box-folder 245: 1-2)
    - General Foods Corporation (Box-folder 245: 3)
    - Germany. White Paper on the Human Rights Situation in Germany and of the Germans in Eastern Europe (Box-folder 245: 4)
    - Great Plains Gasification Associates (Box-folder 245: 5)
    - Hall, Dickler, Lawler, Kent and Howley (law firm) (Box-folder 245: 6)
    - Health (Box-folder 245: 7)
    - Hembre Company (Box-folder 245: 8)
    - Heritage Foundation (Box-folder 245: 9)
    - Housing (Box-folder 245: 10)
    - Hyatt Management Corporation (Box-folder 245: 11)
    - Hyperbar diesel engine (Box-folder 245: 12)
    - Immigration (Box-folder 246: 1)
    - Industrial College of the Armed Forces (Box-folder 246: 2)
    - Inner Circle (organization) (Box-folder 246: 3)
    - Institute for Business Planning (Box-folder 246: 4)
    - Institute for Economic and Legal Analysis
      - Certificates of incorporation (Box-folder 246: 5)
      - Prospectus (Box-folder 246: 6)
      - Correspondence
        - General (Box-folder 246: 7)
        - Alternative Educational Foundation (Box-folder 246: 8)
        - Boarman, Patrick M. (Box-folder 246: 9)
        - Fisher, Antony (Box-folder 246: 10)
        - Pacific Legal Foundation (Box-folder 246: 11)
      - Draft publications
        - Boarman, Patrick M., "The Welfare Juggernaut" (Box-folder 247: 1)
        - Ehrbar, A. F., "An Examination of the Capital Shortage" (Box-folder 247: 2)
        - Fisher, Antony, "Must History Repeat Itself?" (Box-folder 247: 3)
        - Hayek, Friedrich A. von, "Inflation and Unemployment" (Box-folder 247: 4)
        - Jensen, Michael C., "The Debasement of Contracts and the Decline of Capital Markets" (Box-folder 247: 5)
        - Radlauer, David, "A Survey of Public Interest Advocacy" (Box-folder 247: 6)
      - Decline of the West? Conference (proposed) (Box-folder 247: 7)
      - Relevance of Adam Smith Conference (proposed) (Box-folder 247: 8)
      - New York City fiscal crisis project (Box-folder 248: 1-2)
      - Tax status (Box-folder 248: 3)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 248: 4)
    - Institute for Energy Research (Box-folder 248: 5)
    - Institute for Problems of a New International Economic Order (Box-folder 248: 6)
    - Intelligence (Box-folder 249: 1)
    - Intercollegiate Studies Institute (Box-folder 249: 2)
    - International Center for Economic Policy Studies
      - Minutes and brochures (Box-folder 249: 3)
      - Correspondence, memoranda, and printed matter (Box-folder 249: 4)
      - Expense statements (Box-folder 249: 5)
    - International Crude Oil Refineries, Inc. (Box-folder 249: 6)
    - International loans (Box-folder 249: 7)
    - International Rescue Committee
      - Minutes and meeting materials
        - 1976-1977 (Box-folder 249: 8)
        - 1978 (Box-folder 249: 9)
        - 1979 (Box-folder 249: 10)
        - 1980 (Box-folder 250: 1)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 250: 2)
      - Internal circulated documents, relating primarily to Indochinese refugees
        - 1976-1977 (Box-folder 250: 3)
        - 1978 (Box-folder 250: 4-5)
        - 1979 (Box-folder 251: 1)
        - 1980 (Box-folder 251: 2)
        - Material re Latin America (Box-folder 251: 3)
      - Citizens Commission on Indochinese Refugees. The Commission was a subordinate body of the International Rescue Committee
        - Fact-finding mission to Southeast Asia, 1978 February (Box-folder 251: 4-5)
          WJC was co-chairman of the mission.
        - Fact-finding mission to Southeast Asia, 1978 December (Box-folder 252: 1)
          WJC made a trip to Geneva, Switzerland, for related international discussions
        - Report (untitled), 1978 March (Box-folder 252: 2)
      - Annual reports and other issuances (Box-folder 252: 3)
      - Printed matter (Box-folder 252: 4-5)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 253: 1)
    - International securities market (Box-folder 253: 2)
    - International Telephone and Telegraph Corporation. (Box-folder 253: 3)
      Includes material relating to Congressional investigations of government interactions with the corporation and with Robert Vesco
    - Investment Annuity, Inc. (Box-folder 253: 4)
    - Island Capital Company (Box-folder 253: 5-6)
    - Israel (Box-folder 254: 1)
    - Japan (Box-folder 254: 2)
    - Kelso and Company (Box-folder 254: 3-4)
    - Kingsbridge Shopping Plaza (New York City) (Box-folder 254: 5)
    - Knappe and Johnson (company) (Box-folder 254: 6)
    - Knights of Malta (Box-folder 254: 7)
    - Korea (Box-folder 254: 8)
    - Korea Development Bank (Box-folder 254: 9)
    - Langan Aperture Cards, Inc. (Box-folder 254: 10)
    - Laser Link Corporation (Box-folder 254: 11)
    - Lincoln Trust Company (Box-folder 255: 1)
    - Local Government Center (Santa Barbara, California) (Box-folder 255: 2)
    - Long Island Association of Commerce and Industry (Box-folder 255: 3)
    - Long Island Business Review (Box-folder 255: 4)
    - Long Island Forum for Technology
      - Correspondence and minutes (Box-folder 255: 5)
      - Reports (Box-folder 255: 6)
    - Long Island Lighting Company
      - Certificate of incorporation (Box-folder 255: 7)
      - Certificate of environmental compatibility (Box-folder 255: 8)
      - Registration statement and report to Securities and Exchange Commission (Box-folder 256: 1)
      - Annual meeting materials, 1980 (Box-folder 256: 2)
      - Minutes (Box-folder 256: 3)
      - Meeting materials (Box-folder 256: 4)
      - Meeting materials (contd.) (Box-folder 257: 1)
      - Correspondence, memoranda, and press releases (Box-folder 257: 2)
      - Nuclear power project materials (Shoreham Nuclear Power Station) (Box-folder 257: 3)
    - Long Island Rail Road (Box-folder 257: 4)
    - Long Island Trust Company
      - Minutes (Box-folder 257: 5)
      - Financial reports (Box-folder 257: 6)
      - Financial reports (contd.) (Box-folder 258: 1)
      - Correspondence and memoranda (Box-folder 258: 2)
    - Lowry Management Corporation (Box-folder 258: 3)
    - Lyras Properties (Box-folder 258: 4)
    - McGovern (Eugene) estate (Box-folder 258: 5)
    - Main Lafrentz and Company (Box-folder 258: 6)
    - Media law report service (proposed) (Box-folder 258: 7)
    - Merrill Lynch International Bank (Box-folder 258: 8)
    - Metropolitan Club (Washington, D.C.) (Box-folder 258: 9)
    - Middle Eastern railroad (proposed) (Box-folder 258: 10)
    - Modern Age (Box-folder 258: 11)
    - Morality in Media, Inc. (Box-folder 259: 1)
    - Multinational corporations (Box-folder 259: 2)
    - Municipal Securities Rulemaking Board (Box-folder 259: 3)
    - Nassau County (New York)--Taxation issues (Box-folder 259: 4)
    - National Academy of Engineering
      - Colloquium on Industrial Innovation and Public Policy Options (Washington, D.C., 1979) (Box-folder 259: 5)
      - Committee on Technology and International and Economic Trade Issues
        - Correspondence, memoranda, and meeting materials (Box-folder 259: 6)
        - Studies
          - Behrman, Jack N., "TNCs in the NIEO" (Box-folder 259: 7)
          - Cordes, Joseph J., "The Impact of Fiscal and Monetary Policies on Industrial Innovation" (Box-folder 260: 1)
          - Ginsburg, Douglas H., "Antitrust, Uncertainty, and Technological Innovation" (Box-folder 260: 2)
          - Grabowski, Henry G., and John M. Vernon, "The Impact of Regulation on Innovation" (Box-folder 260: 3)
          - Robock, Stefan H., "The International Technology Transfer Process" (Box-folder 260: 4)
        - Background materials (Box-folder 260: 5-6)
    - National Association of Manufacturers (Box-folder 261: 1)
    - National Strategy Information Center (Box-folder 261: 2)
    - New York Republican State Committee (Box-folder 261: 3)
    - New York State Bar Association (Box-folder 261: 4)
    - North American Union (proposed) (Box-folder 261: 5)
    - Nuclear weapons (Box-folder 261: 6)
    - On Top of the World Condominium Development (Clearwater, Florida) (Box-folder 261: 7)
    - On Top of the World Condominium Development (Clearwater, Florida) (contd.) (Box-folder 262: 1)
    - Paris Air Show (Paris, France, 1977) (Box-folder 262: 2)
    - Penril Corporation (Box-folder 262: 3)
    - Piping Rock Club (Locust Valley, New York) (Box-folder 262: 4)
    - Polytechnic Institute of New York (Box-folder 262: 5)
    - Population Action Council (Box-folder 262: 6)
    - Practising Law Institute
      - Correspondence, memoranda, and programs (Box-folder 262: 7)
      - Publications
        - Government Information: Freedom of Information Act, Sunshine Act, Privacy Act (Box-folder 262: 8)
        - The SEC Speaks in 1978
          - Volume I (Box-folder 263: 1)
          - Volume II (Box-folder 263: 2)
          - Supplement (Box-folder 264: 1)
        - Sixth Biennial Conference: Tax Planning for Foundations, Tax-Exempt Status and Charitable Contributions (Box-folder 264: 2)
      - Background materials (Box-folder 264: 3-5)
    - President Ford Library/Museum Fund (Box-folder 265: 1)
    - Price Waterhouse and Company (Box-folder 265: 2)
    - Public interest law (Box-folder 265: 3)
    - Raymond International, Inc. (Box-folder 265: 4)
    - Realtron Corporation (Box-folder 265: 5)
    - Regency Village Associates (Jacksonville, Florida) (Box-folder 265: 6)
    - Reliance Group, Inc. (Box-folder 265: 7)
    - Remac Information Corporation (Box-folder 265: 8)
    - Republican National Committee
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 265: 9)
      - Platform hearing materials and miscellany (Box-folder 266: 1)
      - Council on National Security and International Affairs
        - Correspondence and minutes (Box-folder 266: 2)
        - Reports
          - General (Box-folder 266: 3)
          - "Intelligence and the Role of the Intelligence Community," 1979 (Box-folder 266: 4)
          - Kintner, William R., "Keep the Taiwan Trump," 1978 (Box-folder 266: 5)
          - Kintner, William R., and Robert Strausz-Hupé, "Capturing the Future," 1978 (Box-folder 266: 6)
          - "U.S. Policy for East-West Relations," 1978 (Box-folder 266: 7)
        - Memorandum by WJC re summit meeting in Bonn, West Germany, 1978 July (Box-folder 266: 8)
        - International Economic Affairs Subcommittee. WJC was chairman of the Subcommittee
          - Correspondence and memoranda (Box-folder 266: 9)
          - Report: "A Republican Perspective on U.S. International Economic Policies"
            - Drafts (Box-folder 266: 10)
            - Final version, 1978 April 20 (Box-folder 267: 1)
            - Background materials (Box-folder 267: 2)
    - Responsibilities of lawyers under securities laws (Box-folder 267: 3)
    - Rockefeller family economic empire (Box-folder 267: 4)
    - Rogers and Wells (law firm)
      - Office policies and procedures manual (Box-folder 267: 5)
      - Client lists (Box-folder 267: 6)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 268: 1)
    - S.W.C. Information Corporation (Box-folder 268: 2)
    - St. Francis Hospital (Roslyn, New York)
      - Bylaws (Box-folder 268: 3)
      - Minutes (Box-folder 268: 4)
      - Reports (Box-folder 268: 5)
      - Correspondence and memoranda (Box-folder 269: 1)
      - Brochures and printed matter (Box-folder 269: 2)
    - Salomon Brothers (securities firm) (Box-folder 269: 3)
    - Savile Club (London, England) (Box-folder 269: 4)
    - Scientific Life Systems, Inc.
      - Prospectuses (Box-folder 269: 5)
      - Correspondence, memoranda, and notes (Box-folder 269: 6)
      - Printed matter (Box-folder 270: 1)
    - Scottish Irvine Company (Box-folder 270: 2)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission
      - General (Box-folder 270: 3)
      - Proposed rule changes (Box-folder 270: 4)
      - Study. Theodore A. Levine and Ralph C. Ferrara, "Tradition or Corruption: The Defendants and the Volunteers in the Securities and Exchange Commission's Domestic Questionable Payments Program" (Box-folder 270: 5)
    - Securities industry (Box-folder 271: 1)
    - Shaheen Natural Resources Company (Box-folder 271: 2)
    - Shearson Hayden Stone, Inc. (Box-folder 271: 3)
    - Sky Club (New York City) (Box-folder 271: 4)
    - Small Business Administration
      - General (Box-folder 271: 5)
      - Office policies and procedures manual, 1980 (Box-folder 271: 6)
    - Smith Richardson Foundation (Box-folder 272: 1)
    - Soft lens (optometry) market (Box-folder 272: 2)
    - Solar Shelter Engineering Company (Box-folder 272: 3)
    - Soviet-American relations (Box-folder 272: 4)
    - Special Forces Club (London, England) (Box-folder 272: 5)
    - Special Forces Fund (Box-folder 272: 6)
    - State Insurance Fund (New York) (Box-folder 272: 7)
    - Stirling Partnership (company) (Box-folder 272: 8)
    - Stock option plans (Box-folder 272: 9)
    - Stony Brook Foundation (Box-folder 272: 10)
    - Strategic Arms Limitation Talks (Box-folder 272: 11)
    - Tax guidelines (Box-folder 273: 1)
    - Tax impact on industrial innovation (Box-folder 273: 2)
    - Tax-oriented investments
      - General (Box-folder 273: 3)
      - Florida Gardens Associates (Tampa, Florida) (Box-folder 273: 4)
      - Hatton Associates (Box-folder 273: 5)
    - Tax Reform Act of 1976 and estate planning
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 273: 6)
      - Memoranda (Box-folder 274: 1)
    - Printed matter (Box-folder 274: 2-3)
    - Tax shelters (Box-folder 274: 4)
    - Technology and technology transfer (Box-folder 275: 1-2)
    - Technoserve, Inc. (Box-folder 275: 3)
    - Tender offers (securities) (Box-folder 275: 4)
    - Texaco, Inc. (Box-folder 275: 5)
    - Tri-Rotor Motor Company (Box-folder 275: 6)
    - U.S. News and World Report (Box-folder 276: 1)
    - Union Internationale de la Résistance et de la Déportation (Box-folder 276: 2)
    - Union League Club (New York City) (Box-folder 276: 3)
    - United States Strategic Institute (Box-folder 276: 4)
    - United States Trust Company (Box-folder 276: 5)
    - University Club (Washington, D.C.) (Box-folder 276: 6)
    - Vantage Press (Box-folder 276: 7)
    - Venture capital
      - General (Box-folder 276: 8)
      - Baron Data Systems (company) (Box-folder 276: 9)
      - Halcon International, Inc. (Box-folder 276: 10)
      - International Diagnostic Technology, Inc. (Box-folder 276: 11)
      - KLA Instruments Corporation (Box-folder 277: 1)
      - Lockwood, George S., "An Analysis of Constraints and Stimulants to Aquaculture Development in the United States" (Box-folder 277: 2)
      - Merrill Lynch Economics, Inc. (Box-folder 277: 3)
      - National Venture Capital Association (Box-folder 277: 4)
    - Veterans of the O.S.S. (Box-folder 277: 5)
    - WGBH Educational Foundation (Boston, Massachusetts). Night Watch at Langley television broadcast project (re Central Intelligence Agency)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 277: 6)
      - Proposal (Box-folder 277: 7)
      - First episode draft (Box-folder 278: 1)
      - First episode draft, revised (Box-folder 278: 2)
      - Second episode draft (Box-folder 278: 3)
    - World Association of Lawyers (Box-folder 278: 4)
    - World Authors, Ltd. (Box-folder 278: 5)
    - World Bank (Box-folder 278: 6)
    - World trade
      - General (Box-folder 278: 7-8)
      - Martin, Edwin M., untitled study (Box-folder 278: 9)
    - Worldwide Machinery Corporation (Box-folder 278: 10)
    - ZID Associates (Box-folder 278: 11)
  - Newsletter file, as arranged by WJC (Box-folder 279: 1-3)
  - Clippings (Box-folder 279: 4)
  - Clippings (contd.) (Box 280-281)
  - Clippings (contd.) (Box-folder 282: 1)
  - Miscellany (Box-folder 282: 2)
- REAGAN/BUSH CAMPAIGN FILE, 1980 (Boxes 282-297)